
//Library array for all questions and answers

var library = [
    { //library[0]
        question: "Who has a famous acid-green Quik-Quotes Quill?",
        answer: ["Dolores Umbridge", "Neville Longbottom", "Rita Skeeter"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[1]
        question: "What is the name of the vicious tree that Harry and Ron drove into in 'Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets'?",
        answer: ["The Whomping Willow", "Venomous Tentacula", "Banyan tree"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[2]
        question: "Who was the Whomping Willow planted for?",
        answer: ["James Potter", "Remus Lupin", "Albus Dumbledore"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[3]
        question: "What is Hermione's middle name?",
        answer: ["Ann", "Mary", "Jean"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[4]
        question: "What is the name of Hagrid's huge dog?",
        answer: ["Black", "Fang", "Fido"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[5]
        question: "How much was Dobby paid a month in the Hogwarts kitchen?",
        answer: ["1 sickle", "One Galleon", "17 sickles"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[6]
        question: "What is Dumbledore's sister's name?",
        answer: ["Annie", "Lily", "Ariana"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[7]
        question: "Where did Harry live before his parents died?",
        answer: ["Persil Street", "Privet Drive", "Godric's Hallow"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[9]
        question: "What did Dumbledore leave in his will for Ron?",
        answer: ["Gryffindor's Sword", "Deluminator", "A Book"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[10]
        question: "Who was the half-blood prince?",
        answer: ["Salazar Slytherin", "Voldemort", "Severus Snape"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[11]
        question: "What fruit must you tickle to get into the Hogwarts kitchen?",
        answer: ["A Pear", "An Orange", "A Grape"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[12]
        question: "What shape does Harry's patronus take?",
        answer: ["A Duck", "A Stag", "A Moose"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    },{ //library[13]
        question: "Where did Fleur and Bill meet?",
        answer: ["At the Wesley's House", "Hogwarts", "Gringotts Wizarding Bank"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[14]
        question: "What was the former name of Lord Voldemort?",
        answer: ["Tom Marvolo Riddle", "Thomas Marcell Percevel", "Morak Raymond Thompson"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[15]
        question: "What is the name of the School of Witchcraft that Fleur Delacour attended?",
        answer: ["Doux", "Beauxbatons", "Chaleur"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[16]
        question: "What is the name of the school Victor Krum attended?",
        answer: ["Blagodarja", "Kummerspeck ", "Durmstrang"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[17]
        question: "Who is the poltergist at Hogwarts?",
        answer: ["Peeves", "Grint", "Joyce"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[18]
        question: "What is the name of Mr. Filch's cat?",
        answer: ["Miss Thang", "Mrs. Norris", "Wigglebutt"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    },{ //library[19]
        question: "What is the name of the house that Luna Lovegood is in?",
        answer: ["Griffindor", "Hufflepuff", "Ravenclaw"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[20]
        question: "What is the last name of the three brothers who origanally owned the Deathly Hallows?",
        answer: ["Peverell", "Garcia", "Malvoro"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[21]
        question: "What is the term used for bodies bewitched to do as a Dark wizard bids?",
        answer: ["Hollows", "Inferi", "Deathers"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[22]
        question: "What is the name of the landlord of the Leaky Cauldrons?",
        answer: ["Bertha", "Harry", "Tom"],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[23]
        question: "Which team from the Ministry of Magic is responsible for modifying the memories of Muggles who have been exposed to magic?",
        answer: ["Obliviators", "Aurors", "The Winzengamot"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[24]
        question: "What house was Moaning Myrtle sorted into?",
        answer: ["Hufflepuff", "Ravenclaw", "Gryffindor"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[25]
        question: "Which was the first broom that Harry received as a gift?",
        answer: ["Nimbus 2001", "CleanSweeper", "Nimbus 2000"],
        correctIndexIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[26]
        question: "What patronus does Luna Lovegood has?",
        answer: ["A Rabbit", "A Lion", "A Cow"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[27]
        question: "Who was the quidditch commentator in Harry's first years at Hogwarts?",
        answer: ["Dean Thompson", "Lee Jordan", "Angelina Johnson"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    }, { //library[28]
        question: "Who disguised himself as Mad Eye Moody in The Goblet of Fire?",
        answer: ["Vincent Crab", "Severus Snape", "Barty Crouch Jr."],
        correctIndex: 2,
    }, { //library[29]
        question: "What organization did Hermione start in her 4th year?",
        answer: ["Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare", "Society for Wizards and Elfs Assistant", "Wizards in Peace"],
        correctIndex: 0,
    }, { //library[30]
        question: "What potion did Harry take in order to get Slughorn's memories?",
        answer: ["Polyjuice Potion", "Felix Felicis", "Love Potion"],
        correctIndex: 1,
    },  
]



